©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™ Mobile - + 919815899536
Hello .
Do you live here ?
Nobody lives here .
Where 's Freddy ?
He 's not home .
One , two
Freddy 's coming for you
Three , four
Better lock your door
Five , six
Grab your crucifix
Be calm , Kristen .
Joey !
Kincaid !
Help me !
Aw , shit , Kristen , not again .
I 'm sorry , Kincaid .
Sorry ?
You are one spooked chick .
Thank God .
- I thought for a minute ... - What ?
Dragging us in here ?
Yeah . Cut it out .
You 're putting one serious dent in my beauty sleep .
It 's Freddy . He 's here .
I heard him .
Freddy is dead ... buried and consecrated .
We won , remember ?
He 's coming back for us .
Kincaid 's right .
Fred Krueger 's history .
Come here .
The pipes are cold .
The boiler is cold .
See for yourself .
I don 't know .
How are you , Mr. Johnson ?
That 's nice .
Hi , Kristen . Rick will be out any second .
You going out dressed like that ?
What 's wrong with me this time ?
I 'll just wait by the car .
Me , too .
Something wrong with the stairs ?
It 's avoid all contact day .
What ?
When Dad 's popping aspirin like popcorn ...
it 's avoid all contact day .
Waiting for a limo ?
I 'm off to the club , honey !
Let 's go .
All right , anybody have trig this semester ?
What happened ?
I had a conflict ... homework or " Dynasty " ...
and " Dynasty " won .
Sad story . Soaps will kill you .
Mmm . There 's Dan Jordan .
We are talking one major-league hunk .
You know , you are one major-league hunk .
Thanks , Alice .
Earth to Alice .
Hey , you spacing again ?
Rick , please .
Well , tell you what , he 's a friend of mine .
I 'll introduce you .
Just kidding . But I would introduce her .
All right .
I think I see salvation .
How can you ride this health hazard ?
It 's no wonder that you have asthma .
No , you see , asthma is an inherited condition .
Read a book now and then , you might know something .
Speaking of books , isn 't trig your favorite ?
" Dynasty " again ?
Deb , do us a favor and get a VCR .
Hey , baby ...
you 're sucking on the wrong nozzle .
Hey , yo , needle dick !
I bet you 're the only male in this school ...
suffering from penis envy .
I owe you one .
- So disgusting . - Hey , Supergirl , it 's dead .
Give a bug a break .
- Hi , guys . - Hi , guys ?
That 's all you have to say after last night ?
You better be careful .
He 's coming back .
Listen , little sister ...
you got this freako talent to bring folks into your dream ...
but we don 't need it anymore .
Time to start living like regular people .
Yeah . Let it rest .
Did it ever occur to you if you keep going in ...
you might stir him up again ?
Look , we 'll help you .
We all have better things to dream about .
You got that right ... signed and sealed .
Then what about this ?
That don 't mean dick .
My dog is like me ...
drag him into your crazy dream , and he gets wild .
Here comes your boyfriend .
Can he give you a good night 's sleep ?
We don 't kiss and tell .
How about you guys ?
Look , we 'll talk later , all right ?
Those guys are kinda spooky .
Oh ... then you must think I 'm a total freak .
I go back and forth .
Hey , lighten up .
No one died .
Hi , Dad .
Looking for something ?
Shithead .
I 'm late . I know .
Damn contracts .
Let 's eat .
We waited a long time .
And we gave up , as usual .
You call this vegetation a meal after a ten-hour workday ?
What the hell am I , a rabbit ?
Christ , Alice , try to think a little more .
Yeah , I can think .
I can think of how sick I am ...
of watching you drink your life away ...
and taking it out on me .
I 'm talking to you .
Are you awake or what ?
Dad , don 't start .
Start what ?
Telling the little daydreamer to wake up ?
It 's long overdue .
I don 't need this aggravation .
Jason . Come on , boy , come on .
Come on . That 's a boy .
You almost scared me , boy .
You ugly sucker !
Damn !
This ain 't my dreamland .
If you 're here , I 'm gonna pound your ass !
Fuckin ' " A. "
You shouldn 't have buried me .
I 'm not dead .
Take that , motherfucker !
Kristen , Freddy 's back !
I 'll see you in hell .
Tell ' em Freddy sent ya .
One down ...
two to go .
Wait .
How 's this for a wet dream ?
Kristen ! Help !
Show it !
Hi , guys .
Sorta defeats the purpose , don 't it ?
- What ? - The mirror .
You can 't see yourself in it .
I don 't want to .
You know , if Mom was still alive ...
Dad wouldn 't treat us like this .
Alice , you gotta learn to stand up for yourself .
You know , fight back .
Like that . It 's all in the mind .
You see yourself doing something ...
and your body reacts and does it .
Like so .
Like that . Now you do it .
Me ? No , I can 't .
- Yeah , you can . - No , I can 't .
Yes , you can . Just get up there and just ...
Like that . Big and strong . Do it .
Good , but , Alice-san ...
you must have balance .
So go to it .
Swish . Killed a fish .
Joey , I 'm getting tired of picking up your clothes .
And this crap ...
I wish you 'd turn it off .
Here you are .
Where were you this morning ?
Rick 's looking all over .
Have you seen Joey and Kincaid ?
I can 't find them .
I 'm sure they 're around .
Well , I 'm not so sure .
We have matching luggage again .
The bags under your eyes .
Nightmares ?
God , I hate dreaming .
I love to dream .
I just hate the ones about my dad .
How do you handle your nightmares ?
My mom taught me when I was little .
Did you ever hear of the dream master ?
Sounds like a game show host to me .
No , it 's a rhyme .
Just have to dream about someplace fun .
Remember , you 're in control .
How do you know so much about dreams ?
When it 's all you have , you kinda become an expert .
We better get going ...
before your brother starts a search party .
Anyway , Kafka and Goethe have never been irreconcilable .
Kris , where were you ?
- Hey , what ... - He killed them !
What ? Wait ! Calm down !
Hey , somebody help her .
Feeling better now ?
Yeah , I guess so .
What happened ?
You had quite a nasty bump .
I gotta get out of here !
Now , now , now .
You stay put .
You need to rest .
You don 't get it .
He 's after me .
It 's OK , honey .
I wanna draw some blood .
Feeling better now ?
What happened ?
You had quite a nasty bump .
You seen Rick around ?
You are his sister , right ?
Rick stayed late after school .
Kristen wasn 't feeling very well .
Could you tell him I 'm looking for him ?
Oh , by the way , I 'm Dan .
Sorry , Alice .
Your shift 's over . My table now .
Hi , guys . Hi , Dan .
How are you doing ?
Hi . Can I get just a Coke and some fries ?
Do you wanna hear our specials , or do you want any dessert ?
Oh , hi , handsome . Care for some buns ?
- Here . - You in a hurry ?
Gotta get to the library before it closes .
Killer physics test .
I know . I hardly have any time to study .
Maybe you shouldn 't be working here so much .
You don 't want to wait tables the rest of your life .
I know . It 's my greatest fear .
You know , he is so cute .
- I wonder where he works out ? - Save it , Deb .
I mean , there is life after exercise .
One of these days ...
I 'm gonna set you up with a real guy ...
teach you to get your priorities straight .
I think Sheila 's more interested ...
in dissecting bodies than their outsides .
Give her time .
Her hormones will kick in some day .
Deb , later in life , you 'll appreciate my motto .
What 's that ?
Mind over matter .
I 'll see you later , OK ?
Alice , can you leave here ?
What 's wrong ?
Kincaid and Joey died last night .
What ?
Hey , Rick , come here !
Stay with her .
Kristen , what happened ?
Look , you 're gonna hear all kinds of stories .
And after all we 've been through together ...
how could I let him get to them ?
We were a team .
I 'm gonna get that son of a bitch .
Who ?
Rick , we gotta go .
- Now . - I 'm coming .
Before it 's too late .
I gotta go . I guess I 'll talk to you later .
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
So , why the haunted house ?
It 's not just a house .
It 's his home .
He 's waiting in there for me to dream .
Hey , it 's OK .
We 're with you .
I told you , you can 't help me .
This isn 't a normal nightmare .
I 'm history .
I don 't get it .
- Come on . - Jeez . What 'd I miss ?
She told us a story about Freddy .
Fred Krueger . He 's a town legend .
He was a child killer freed on a technicality .
So ?
So , a lot of parents got pissed off ...
and , according to Kris ...
they hunted him down and roasted him ...
like a Thanksgiving turkey .
Nice neighborhood .
Anyway , that 's where it gets weird .
She says that he comes back in dreams .
And if he kills you in your dream ...
you 're dead for real .
Now I lay me down to sleep .
The master of dreams , my soul I 'll keep .
Dream master . I think I remember the rhyme .
Kristen , get the hell away from that house !
¡ Andale !
You don 't have to go if you don 't want to .
I 'll take care of you .
I better go .
OK ...
but I 'll call you tonight , and we 'll get through this .
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
Shotgun .
Something the matter with the cuisine ?
Well , Mom , I 'll tell you ...
when two of your friends die in the same day ...
let me know what it does to your appetite .
You 're just tired .
Don 't think I haven 't noticed you aren 't sleeping .
That has got to stop , honey .
What 's wrong with me ?
Adolescent anxiety .
That 'll make it better .
Oh , God .
Mom , what did you do ?
Jesus ! Sleeping pills ?
Look , Kristen , I 'm sorry .
Sorry ?
Sorry that you and your tennis pals ...
torched this guy , and now he 's after me ?
In case you haven 't been keeping score ...
it 's his fucking banquet , and I 'm the last course !
We went over this in therapy !
No , Mother .
You just murdered me .
Take that to your goddamn therapy .
Dream someplace fun .
Thanks , Alice .
Hi , little girl .
- What 's your name ? - Alice .
I have a friend named Alice .
Elm Street 's last brat .
Farewell .
We beat you before !
And now you 're all alone !
Kristen , why don 't you ...
call on one of your little friends ?
Maybe they could help .
Never !
I 'm the last !
Why don 't you reach out ...
and cut someone ?
How sweet .
Fresh meat .
Alice , wake up and get out !
Alice , I 'm so sorry .
It was a mistake .
I pulled you in .
Alice , come to Daddy .
Leave her alone , you son of a bitch !
Now no one sleeps .
The souls of my children .
You 'll need my power .
Are you OK ?
Kristen ... we 've gotta get to her house !
Oh , God ! Kristen !
Let me go .
Hi , Alice . Wish you were here .
Your horrible brother 's up to his old tricks .
Rick , as long as I 've known you , I 've always wanted to ask ...
what the hell this shit is you put in your hair .
I want his body .
That 's bullshit . What else do you want ?
She wants my body .
Alice , what are you doing ?
I don 't know .
It makes me feel better .
What are you doing ?
Hello , baby .
Great .
You made her so happy then .
Until all this Freddy shit .
Why didn 't I just stay with her ?
It wouldn 't have made any difference .
Sure it would have .
No . I saw it happen in my dream .
There was this horrible man .
I don 't wanna hear about Freddy , OK ?
I heard it all from Kristen , so stop it .
I could smell the smoke .
I could feel the heat from the fire .
- It wasn 't a dream ! - Just stop it !
She wasn 't crazy and neither are you ...
so just cut it out . Please .
Jeez . Why are you acting this way ?
I don 't know , Rick .
I just feel so different .
Something happened in the dream .
And now it 's like part of her is with me .
I love you , too !
Hello , everyone !
Girl , I am so dead on my feet .
We have matching luggage .
What do you mean ?
You didn 't sleep last night ?
It 's that obvious , huh ?
- Then you saw him , too . - Saw who ?
I was up all night cramming for that physics test .
Oh , and I put this little baby together .
You know Deb 's afraid of bugs .
I made it for her .
Ultrahigh sound waves .
It 'll make ' em run , screaming their antennas off .
Look , I 'll see you in class , OK ?
I don 't smoke .
All right , you 've got forty minutes .
So good luck . Go for it .
Help me !
Help !
Wake up !
Wake up , damn it !
Wanna suck face ?
Sheila , wake up !
You flunked .
Give her her thing .
Didn 't you see it ?
He was here .
What are you talking about ?
He was here !
Step back , please .
Stand back .
Asthma attack ?
What 17-year-old has fatal asthma ?
God , she was gonna be a doctor .
It was Freddy .
Enough with that crap !
I saw it . It was my dream .
I brought Sheila in .
Oh , God .
I brought Sheila in like Kristen did with me .
No , don 't !
I gave Sheila to him !
And now she 's dead !
I really think Kristen 's story is getting to her .
Dan , I really don 't know if it 's a story .
Look at us .
We 're dropping off like flies here .
- Good seeing you . - Bye .
Come on .
Excuse me , miss .
Can I get a pack of gum ?
Hey . Where you been ?
I haven 't seen you around .
I 've been working double shifts .
Guess you need the extra money , huh ?
Look , you know why .
You don 't want to believe me .
Don 't you understand ?
I can 't sleep .
Someone might die .
Let 's say that this is real , right ?
Why , all of a sudden , is this Freddy guy after you ?
Kristen was the last child left of the people who killed Freddy .
Maybe Freddy can 't get to the new kids ...
unless there 's someone to bring them to him .
We 're gonna be late for the drive-in .
I have to get back .
I guess I 'll see you later .
Ninety-three days till summer vacation , man .
- You tired ? - No . Worried .
Let 's see if we can make it until summer .
It 's like open season around here .
Pretty weird stuff .
Speaking of weird , you gotta feel for that guy .
Dead girlfriend , basket case for a sister ...
Shut up , asshole !
What a dick .
You know ...
You look wasted , man .
I 've been up with Alice .
Hey , how 's she doing ?
I saw her last night at the diner .
She 's blaming herself for Sheila .
I know how she feels .
I think about Kristen all the time .
Maybe I could have stopped it if I 'd have listened .
You mean Freddy ?
What else ?
You ever take a look at our town 's history ?
It 's not exactly a safe place to be a teenager .
Hey , bozos , let 's hustle ... now .
Well , if I 'm next , watch your back , man .
Where were we ?
Every society , dating back to the ancients ...
has had theories regarding dreams .
What they mean , how to control them .
Aristotle believed during sleep your soul roams free .
What it sees are dreams .
The skilled dreamers are able to control what they see .
There is a myth that there 's two gates your soul can enter .
One is a positive gate ...
the other a negative gate .
The key element is that there 's a dream master ...
someone who guards the positive gate ...
and , in fact , protects the sleeping host .
Taken altogether , they offer a fascinating perspective ...
on ancient history .
Those of you who don 't find it fascinating ...
you better listen up , because it 's on the final .
Rick , make me laugh .
Going down .
What ?
A true warrior needs no eyes .
Come on out and fight me , you chickenshit !
Ninja warriors have calm .
Find your balance , Rick !
Too wimpy to show yourself , Krueger ?
Well , how 's this for balance ?
Banzai .
How you gonna fight me without your weapon , Freddy ?
Sayonara , Rick-san !
Though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death ...
I shall fear no evil ...
for Thou art with me with Thy rod and Thy staff .
They comfort me .
Dearly bereaved , we gather here in remorse for Rick Johnson ...
a young man whose death confounds and mystifies us ...
for Rick was in his prime , beloved by all ...
exemplary of young men 's ideals ...
and of strong moral fiber .
We grieve our loss but take comfort in knowing such a man ...
rests in the kingdom of God .
Let our faith supersede our knowledge ...
for truly the Lord works in mysterious ways .
Hello , baby !
I love this .
They think I 'm dead , don 't they ?
This is great .
Hey . What 's with the tears ?
I wouldn 't leave ya .
Come on , don 't cry .
I 'm here . It was a big joke to fool Freddy .
Come on , smile for me .
No more daydreams .
Well , gotta go .
Good night .
You OK ?
Not really .
Is there anything we can do ?
I don 't think so .
I guess this is my own war .
No , it 's not .
We all have to survive .
I mean , I don 't spend hours working out ...
to let some night stalker beat me .
You don 't really get it .
He 's not a night stalker .
And it 'll take more than bench presses to beat him .
So what do we do ?
Let 's go over to Debbie 's tonight .
We have to make a plan .
I got to go .
How about I pick you up at the diner at 8 : 00 ?
Here . It 's a good luck charm .
Brings bad luck to the creep you flatten with it .
This is it .
Mind over matter .
Mind over matter ?
Sheila used to say that .
God , every day , she changes .
No . It 's after every death .
What 's happening to me ?
Alice , where are you going ?
Just to see Debbie .
No , you 're not .
I want you to stay in .
Dad , I gotta go , and there 's nothing you can do about it .
You have no right to stop me .
If you just knew what was going on .
I know very much what 's going on with you and your friends .
Everybody thinks they know , but they don 't .
Look at me , Alice .
I lost Rick because I didn 't watch him .
I don 't want to lose you .
We 're all we have .
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
All the towns in America ...
and I gotta move to the Bermuda Triangle .
That 's great .
See ya , Alvin .
Hey , he ain 't no paper man .
Why , don 't you know him ?
That 's " Hot Fingers " Curly .
Boy , he really swings out hoppin ' with a jive .
- You want to dance ? - Do I ?
What 'll it be ?
Come on , honey .
I don 't want to be here forever .
If the food don 't kill ya , the service will .
Help us , Alice !
The usual .
No , Alice , don 't let him do it !
My favorite .
No ! Come on , no !
Eeney , meeney , miney ...
Come on , no !
Moe !
No , Alice , don 't let him do it !
Rick , you little meatball .
I love soul food .
No ! No ! Stop !
Bring me more .
Your shift is over .
Come on . We have to hurry !
- What 's going on ? - I 'm driving .
He 's going after Debbie .
I 've got to stop him .
We got to stop him .
I 'm with you on this thing .
I want to help you .
I 'm on your side , OK ?
Here we are .
Come on . We have to hurry !
- What 's going on ? - I 'm driving .
I don 't believe in you .
I believe in you .
No pain ... no gain .
He 's going after Debbie .
I 've got to stop him .
Help me !
Here we are .
Come on . We have to hurry !
What 's going on ?
I 'm driving .
He 's going after Debbie .
I 've got to stop him .
I get the weirdest feeling we 've done this before .
Come on . We have to hurry .
I 'm driving .
Oh , my God .
We 're both asleep .
He 's got us going in circles .
We got to go !
You can check in , but you can 't check out .
What the hell was that ?
She 's gone .
I 've collected her like the others .
All right , I 'm gonna punch his ticket in .
I 'm sorry .
All right , get him in there .
Base , this is med seven .
We have a male Caucasian , 16-18 years of age .
Multiple lacerations about the head and neck area .
Possible internal injuries .
What 's that do ?
Relaxes your boyfriend .
Put the needle down .
Rules is rules .
He stays awake !
Those are my rules , understand ?
Are you nuts ?
He 's allergic , OK ?
You should have said something in the first place .
Damn kids .
Don 't let them put you to sleep .
We have to get ready for him .
When does he have surgery ?
Fifteen minutes .
Let him be , Alice !
They 're gonna kill him !
What are you talking about ?
Let me go !
Alice ! Damn it !
Get back here !
Come on !
No . No gas .
No gas . No . Don 't put ...
Fuckin ' " A. "
Well , it ain 't Dr. Seuss .
Get away from him , you son of a bitch !
- I saw him . He was here . - I know .
We have to get out of this place .
Out for a spin , lovebirds ?
Dan , hold on !
Alice , it 's too late .
He 's hemorrhaging .
Bring him out of it ! Hurry !
You got to put me back under now !
Relax , son . It was rough , but we pulled you out .
You 're gonna be OK .
One , two , Freddy 's coming for you
Three , four , better lock your door
Five , six , grab your crucifix
Seven , eight , better stay up late
Nine , ten , never sleep again
Welcome to Wonderland , Alice .
You 've got their power .
I 've got their souls .
Come on .
Banzai .
You think you 've got what it takes ?
I 've been guarding my gate for a long time , bitch .
I am eternal .
Now I lay me down to sleep .
The master of dreams , my soul I 'll keep .
In the reflection of my mind 's eye ...
Evil will see itself , and it shall die !
Let them out !
You 're dead , Krueger .
Thank you , Alice .
You saved us .
Freedom .
Rest in hell .
You know , I slept through all of last night ...
and I haven 't done that in days .
I 'm still having trouble .
I can sleep two , maybe three hours , if I 'm lucky .
I don 't mind , though .
I have more reasons to stay awake now .
Come on .
Make a wish .
Come on , you don 't believe in that stuff .
Yeah , I do , and I think you do , too .
Here it goes .
What 'd you wish for ?
If I tell you , it won 't come true .
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ